[Music]
i'm delighted to uh
accept the emerging company of the year
award uh on behalf of my team
at iceland i would like to thank the
organizing
team at economic times the entire times
group
and the eminent jury for giving us this
honor and i would like to dedicate this
award to
our 26 million customers more than 100
000 distribution partners
and more than 10 000 employees who make
ici
lumber the company it is
since 2001 when the industry got opened
up
the insurance industry has made
tremendous progress
and i see this award also a recognition
of the role the industry plays in the
economy at large
our journey at iceland also started in
19 years back and in a sense we are just
emerging
out of our teenage years into young
adulthood
as we get into the energetic 20s
i hope and wish that we remain as
youthful
as curious and as emerging in the days
ahead
thank you again